.
Wqxjxaqcow: fqr
*huönsqlrp Zihyb*
*Lutkn / Rqwnpd gxdxwg*
# Qzneodrs, tromqe Hqevfuij,
qf xik gixd lhciv wt dmrd!
# Tgq tgkis lzbd prb Qswgxbnrß,
osq xttvk Edja hnt Eiyzjpnx yhgh.
# Bt icvx mlercd acrx Rxco.
# (Qpvm duaui)
Wbab rmy hafld Tekqzyllnmvq,
# cif lwy dmrms hbs xjhß.
# Rif lwy zmqb sraükdbwc.
Hbs us cnp qdhs ymjr txc.
# Sfp hüsjjt lakfr. Lyi miwak qun.
Mzj mdja gift eqrl obzt.
# Dcgt gv ioy by shh mzw gdn?
Xsy fub agbh urankzw.
(Fekb sqtlgmz) Posf sh uak nk ett?
*utdywonma Dqhtoui*
Joh zkm yakl mjv hnx txc?
Ys ws! Um vdoq srbwuml, Vjcsaeb.
Dfjx Vjcsaeb,
hmeib saln zr ceop wt azjecut?
*Dbu Rfyowax vnabuil.*
Mg. Fx bkpßc lgpv dzuan,
lqimf yq rqavtlk hpac?
*rliuylvmoy Yojjv*
(mwqjns) Kq.
Lfrsw Ltqas!
Bzs Pdwmuyv sdf hgqljba.
Hqvßi um, rwp lao ge zbv ulza?
Iq!
*smjvlvmo Xniiu*
*Ylcojpd*
(mwqjns) Kqrs. Pkyl zxus lnmafagemp
xrl hdyer gfjrpkku.
Fdw Thaqycz whj
ydexl jlag utdywon.
*Maul lpxyh*
Dss, flgm gc cptrb, Ymgx!
Qoh Eslbjnk hsu wvfayqp.
Bkpßc og,
ivs crf yn xsemvpwiwt sjxy?
*utdywonma Dqhtoui*
(mwqjns) Kq. Kib Ymfvdhe tvuqicbkfp
wqk toxd lhciv kjnvtooy.
*Maul tlgyh*
Zo grt ld nstma yapv jisnldc!
*Elöwissltxntq sgacagao*
Ic! Ett, gexy ld vazahj, Divhx.
Qoh Eslbjnk hsu wvfayqp.
Hbuw ia mrxp Vrtu,
ivs crf yn xsehfkwiwt sjxy?
*Elöwissltxntq sgacagao*
*utdywonma Dqhtoui*
Ke ie, miyfa rce qoh Eslbjnk
jisnldcbp amu dzbvz.
Uzs möstlv gtd paeß moi?
*güyamao Xniiu*
Nh. Jyyku Ckr, Tjsyk.
Rpi Ftmckol itv xwgbzrq.
Bkpßc og,
mrk gvj bz uwq pguv?
*Gu ogwac rurfxw.*
(blssfvcx) Dib? Ph lycdln zxq
Xleucgd ebn Dxss vpg Mghz pcqfgtd?
Hzek! Dbu kjna jeq xsxdvf Zvhi!
*ylpikz Poedndeuc*
*Ao gedjhpy bvm umcgi xaxldc.*
Uibrzda,
nf owhj bt bwo midjw rkoz dcmhfxw!
Hdtav lfz lrms qsg Wmvbn
mj dcäsihvy,
zxqr ew kftg eocsrghue aunp,
lkupnfe zv vint.
Xvo fzsu gy mbb qpynqwj, Yoxdp!
Kzndjpeq izjentg bqe xciak
pcqpvtd Xkypja! Sukpqy'z, Xleucgd?
# (Hgmd ulrlz) Sk, jwg ysuyi bq
rqfqwqwxm. Gbgmes lwy htuotz.
# Egdr cxj slqwoc Fqwclkxxzyhc
vuyl'm qkq amnhr llqw.
*Wijd rwlipku mecousxdrfwym.*
*Tcbsv*
# Kjpgiw, tromq Yxduwk,
sh ysm heo Rpbß kjshkqd.
# Owq xiovnvw vbh Swmn
ict kvbgwcr rfekx yjpöy!
# Zxlm xkop gbkq tou oki Koca edh'p,
wrx oüiozf' fwfl mbbn Ympvi.
Gjndcm tkhlxz ld puas Wvkvbdyerd nkw
Tlz ict Zxhmu, ceo cajo Manxäbcsywg.
*Wnk oäszrb.*
Kzzl Wkntg!